//questions array for global variable
const questionsArray = [
  //question 0
  {
    questionText: 'A bird in the hand is worth two in the ____.',
    questionChoice: ['Tree', 'Nest', 'Bush', 'Cage'],
    questionAnswer: 'Bush',
  },
  //question 1
  {
    questionText: 'That is/isn’t really my cup of ____.',
    questionChoice: ['Coffee', 'Tea', 'Joe', 'Soup'],
    questionAnswer: 'Tea'
  },
  //question 2
  {
    questionText: 'I’m so excited, I’ll be there with ____ on!',
    questionChoice: ['Bells', 'Goats', 'Shoes', 'Hats'],
    questionAnswer: 'Bells',
  },
  // //question 3
  {
    questionText: 'Looks like the ____ is out of the bag now!',
    questionChoice: ['Secret', 'Mystery', 'Snake', 'Cat'],
    questionAnswer: 'Cat',
  },
  //question 4
  {
    questionText: 'I’m ____ over ____ in love!',
    questionChoice: ['Face, Foot', 'Head, Heels', 'Head, Bottom', 'Head, Feet'],
    questionAnswer: 'Head, Heels',
  },
  //question 5
  {
    questionText: 'I’m as ____ as a clam',
    questionChoice: ['Calm', 'Sheltered', 'Happy', 'Collected'],
    questionAnswer: 'Happy',
  },
  //question 6
  {
    questionText: 'Pardon my ____',
    questionChoice: ['French', 'Outburst', 'English', 'Forks'],
    questionAnswer: 'French',
  },
  //question 7
  {
    questionText: 'I work hard to bring home the ____!',
    questionChoice: ['Bread', 'Bacon', 'Cash', 'Milk'],
    questionAnswer: 'Bacon',
  },
  //question 8
  {
    questionText: 'Are we going to talk about the ____ in the room?',
    questionChoice: ['Unicorn', 'Dragon', 'Elephant', 'Mouse'],
    questionAnswer: 'Elephant',
  },
  //question 9
  {
    questionText: 'Tonight we are going to paint the town ____!',
    questionChoice: ['Bright', 'Silver', 'Gold', 'Red'],
    questionAnswer: 'Red',
  },
  //question 10
  {
    questionText: 'You’re the bee’s ____!',
    questionChoice: ['Knees', 'Sting', 'Honey', 'Wing'],
    questionAnswer: 'Knees',
  },

];
